<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://ivioletsss.github.io/Huminex/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://ivioletsss.github.io/Huminex/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-07-17T13:06:22+00:00</updated><id>https://ivioletsss.github.io/Huminex/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Huminex</title><subtitle>The Huminex lab is a research group deeply committed to exploring how intelligent technologies can responsibly enhance human emotion, cognition, and behavior. The lab grew out of an student-led human-centered computing club started by Lili Zhang during her undergraduate years at Hainan University. Our mission is to designing adaptive and embodied systems to ethically intervene in human experience without diminishing autonomy, to enhance well-being and promote equitable human– technology futures.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="https://ivioletsss.github.io/Huminex/2025/07/17/2024-02-23-example-post-3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2025-07-17T13:06:22+00:00</published><updated>2025-07-17T13:04:45+00:00</updated><id>https://ivioletsss.github.io/Huminex/2025/07/17/2024-02-23-example-post-3</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ivioletsss.github.io/Huminex/2025/07/17/2024-02-23-example-post-3.html"><![CDATA[<p>Text-to-image (T2I) models enable users worldwide to create high-definition and realistic images through text prompts, where the underrepresentation and potential misinformation of images have raised growing concerns. However, few existing works examine cultural representativeness, especially involving whether the generated content can fairly and accurately reflect global cultures. Combining automated and human methods, we investigate this issue in multiple dimensions quantificationally and conduct a set of evaluations on three prevailing T2I models (DALL-E v2, Stable Diffusion v1.5 and v2.1). Introducing attributes of cultural cluster and subject, we provide a fresh interdisciplinary perspective to bias analysis. The benchmark dataset UCOGC is presented, which encompasses authentic images of unique cultural objects from global clusters.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author></entry></feed>